sqlteam.com 2010-05-04

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is effective May 14th, 2007.

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the SQLTeam.com website. On some pages you are able to enter personal information and post content on the site. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Email Address
  * Name
  * Country
  * Etc.

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you email an article to another individual we will ask for their email address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

  * Email Address

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when registering in the forums to complete that registration. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the registration.

We use the information you provide about someone else when forwarding content only to forward the content. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that process.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by updating your profile in the forums. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use the [Contact Us](http://www.sqlteam.com/contactus.aspx) to reach us.

| 

\- Advertisement -

\- Sponsor's Message -

## SQLShare.com Videos

### [Retrieving a List of Reports from Reporting Services](http://www.sqlshare.com/RetrievingaListofReportsfromReportingServices_760.aspx)

There's nothing quite as elegant as a data driven solution, as least if you're a DBA type person! If you're using Reporting Services the list of all the reports is stored in a table, no need for fancy SOAP or scripting, just query the table and get the list. Not a complex query at all, but a powerful technique to know

### [Performance Tuning Puzzle - Part 2](http://www.sqlshare.com/PerformanceTuningPuzzlePart2_759.aspx)

In this follow up to our puzzle we look at the impact of adding a recommended index, try an experiment with hard coding values, and finally rewrite the query slightly to try to get the performance we want. We started at 580 reads, and at completion we're down to 21, a nice gain! It shows some of the ideas behind tuning, and it shows that even getting performance from a simple query may take some thought.

### [Performance Tuning Puzzle - Part 1](http://www.sqlshare.com/PerformanceTuningPuzzlePart1_758.aspx)

Tuning takes practice, right? Well, here's your chance. We've got a fairly simple query that just returns a count, and with our default setup this query is not cheap - can you fix it? Can you get it from 700+ reads to 200? To less than 10? The references link for this video contains the database (SQL 2008) and the query, just attach the database and see what you can do. In the next view we'll look at some of the steps you might take to get warp speed from this query.

### [Performance Tuning Puzzle - Part 1](http://www.sqlshare.com/PerformanceTuningPuzzlePart1_758.aspx)

Tuning takes practice, right? Well, here's your chance. We've got a fairly simple query that just returns a count, and with our default setup this query is not cheap - can you fix it? Can you get it from 700+ reads to 200? To less than 10? The references link for this video contains the database (SQL 2008) and the query, just attach the database and see what you can do. In the next view we'll look at some of the steps you might take to get warp speed from this query.

### [An Introduction to Check Constraints](http://www.sqlshare.com/AnIntroductiontoCheckConstraints_757.aspx)

Check constraints are a great way to enforce additional logic at the row level, perhaps making sure that a gender column only includes the values M or F. The constraint can reference multiple columns, but only within the same row, and you have the option to NOT enforce it against existing data. A useful technique to know!  
  
---|---
